arlingtonmazda.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy

Your privacy is important to Rosenthal Automotive, as is your trust in our products and services. We want you to know that the information you share with us will be treated with care.

Rosenthal Automotive's Privacy Statement for U.S. Consumers lets you know how we handle personally identifiable information you share with Rosenthal Automotive through rosenthalauto.com and certain other Rosenthal Automotive Websites (e.g., rosenthalchevrolet.com, rosenthalchrysler.com, rosenthaljeep.com, arlingtonmazda.com, landmarkhonda.com, fairfaxhonda.com, rosenthalhonda.com, rosenthaljaguar.com, rosenthallandrover.com, jaguarchantilly.com. landroverchantilly.com, rosenthalacura.com, gaithersburgmazda.com, fairfaxvw.com, fairfaxvolvo.com); It also applies to information about you and your vehicle we obtain from Rosenthal affiliates sites. Rosenthal Automotive, our affiliates, our licensees, and dealers may use the information you share with us. It may be used by our suppliers exclusively to provide services for Rosenthal Automotive, and by our business partners to conduct joint marketing programs with Rosenthal Automotive. **We will not share your personal information with third parties other than these, or with any third party for their independent use without your permission.**

Rosenthal Automotive businesses covered by this Privacy Statement include:

BMW of Alexandria  
Audi of Alexandria (soon to be Audi of Arlington)  
Porsche of Arlington  
Fiat of Alexandria  
Rosenthal Arlington Mazda  
Rosenthal Landmark Honda  
Rosenthal Fairfax Honda  
Rosenthal Fairfax Volkswagen  
Rosenthal Fairfax Volvo  
Rosenthal Jaguar of Tysons  
Rosenthal Land Rover of Tysons  
Rosenthal Jaguar of Chantilly  
Rosenthal Land Rover of Chantilly  
Rosenthal Acura  
Rosenthal Gaithersburg Mazda 

#### Information Collection

Rosenthal Automotive may obtain information about you and your vehicle in a number of ways: For example, our Websites, sweepstakes entries, test-drive registrations, surveys, vehicle sales records, and other public sources. While you may use Rosenthal Automotive's websites to learn about our products and services without disclosing any information about you or your vehicle, we may ask you to provide us with personal information including:

contact information (name, address, city, state and Zip Code, e-mail address, and telephone number)  
vehicle information (vehicle identification number (VIN), make, model, model year, mileage, etc.)  
demographic information (age range, marital status, household composition, etc.)  
non-credit-related marketing profile information (when you plan to purchase or lease; the vehicle in which you're interested, etc.)

In addition, Rosenthal Automotive affiliates, and other sources such as those that provide lists of potential vehicle purchasers or current owners may give the information they have regarding you or your vehicle to us so that we may serve your needs better.

#### Uses

Information about you or your vehicle may be used to respond to your requests for product brochures, to customize and improve communication content, or for marketing or product research. It may also be used to provide you with helpful offers and information on Rosenthal Automotive products and services. We may share information about you and your vehicle within Rosenthal Automotive and with our affiliates. Rosenthal Automotive may also share personal information collected with our suppliers for the exclusive purpose of providing services for us (for example, mailing information in response to your request for a vehicle brochure) and with our business partners to conduct joint marketing programs with Rosenthal Automotive.

**Rosenthal Automotive will not share information about you or your vehicle with any third party for their independent use without your permission.**

We may disclose information about you or your vehicle as required by law, in conjunction with a government inquiry, or in litigation or dispute resolution.

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Devices

We may use cookies and other tracking devices on our Websites. Using cookies on our sites provides benefits to you, such as allowing you to maintain your account information between visits. The use of cookies also allows us to measure site activity to provide a better user experience. Cookies and other tracking devices may be used to tell us the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our site, the site you visited just before coming to ours, and the name of your Internet service provider.

We may use third parties to serve Rosenthal Automotive advertisements on other Websites. In serving Rosenthal Automotive advertisements, these companies may use cookies and other tracking devices to collect certain information about your visits to other Websites (such as browser type, IP address, which page was visited, and time of day). This information may be used to evaluate our online advertising campaigns or to tailor promotions and other marketing messages to you. You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and how to manage their use.

#### Remarketing with Google Analytics

Rosenthal Automotive uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.

Please visit Google to obtain additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.

#### Changes

We retain the right to change this Privacy Statement. We will post changes to this page in a timely manner.

This statement is effective as of 8/1/2008.
